Guide to the Joe Conzo, Jr. photographs and ephemera, 1977-present.
Conzo, Joe, Jr. photographs and ephemera,
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Joe Conzo, Jr. photographs and ephemera, 1977-present.
8091
Joe, Conzo
Ca. 6 cubic feet.
4.1 terabytes.
Photographs, ephemera, printed material, flyers.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Collection includes photographic film negatives, 4x6 and 8x10 prints, proof and contact sheets, large format finished prints, and associated ephemera. Many of the images have been digitized and arrived on hard drives.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Joe Conzo, Jr. is an American photographer, born in the Bronx, New York City in 1963. In 1978, while attending South Bronx High School, Conzo became friends with members of the Cold Crush Brothers, an important and influential early Hip Hop group which included DJs Charlie Chase and Tony Tone and MCs Grandmaster Caz, JDL, Easy AD, and Almighty KayGee. Conzo became the group's personal photographer, documenting their live performances at the T-Connection, Disco Fever, Harlem World, the Ecstasy Garage, and the Hoe Avenue Boy's Club. He also took pictures of other Hip Hop artists and groups, including The Treacherous 3, The Fearless 4, and The Fantastic 5. As a result, he captured some of the earliest images of Hip Hop culture, along with every day street scenes and Latin music performances and events between 1977 and 1984. Joe Conzo is currently a Medical Technician with the New York City Fire Department, and is active in leadership of the EMTs labor union. He continues to photograph Hip Hop and other music performers both nationally and internationally.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Collection includes photographic film negatives, 4x6 and 8x10 prints, proof and contact sheets, large format finished prints, and associated ephemera. Many of the images have been digitized and arrived on hard drives.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Conzo, Joe, Jr.; Cornell University Library Hip-Hop Collection.
Subjects:
Hip-hop -- History. -- United States; Hip-hop -- History -- United States; Rap musicians -- United States; Disc jockeys.; Hip-hop dance.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to negatives restricted to the permission of the curator.
Access to Box 4, Folder 3 restricted to permission of the curator.
RELATED MATERIALS
Associated online resource: call number TR654.C66.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Photographs
Subseries I.a. Large Format Prints - Cold Crush Brothers
Subseries I.b. Large Format Prints - Bronx, N.Y. Scenes
Subseries I.c. 8 x 10 Prints - Modern, Reprints
Subseries I.d. 8 x 10 Prints - Contemporary to original photo date
Subseries I.e. 4 x 6 Prints - Cold Crush Brothers
Subseries I.f. 4 x 6 Prints - Bronx, N.Y. Scenes
Series II. Contact Sheets, Negatives, and Slides
Series III. Related Materials
Series IV. Born in the Bronx
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Photographs
  - Large Format Prints - Cold Crush Brothers
    - Easy A.D. & Tony Tone, 1981 (Box 9)
      Posed Studio Shot, taken at United Bronx Parents
    - Tony Tone and Kool Herc at T-Connection, 1979; Two copies (Box 9)
      Tony Tone and Kool Herc posing with crossed arms backstage at T-Connection
    - Tony Tone at T-Connection, 1979; Framed Item 12
      Tony Tone looking through record crates
    - Cold Crush Brothers T-Connection, 1979 (Box 9)
      Cold Crush Brothers on stage
    - Cold Crush Brothers, 1980 (Box 9)
      Cold Crush Brothers posing on the street
    - Fans of the Cold Crush Brothers vs. Fantastic Romantic 5 battle, Harlem World, 1981 (Box 9)
      Three Fans with Cold Crush shirts at the famous 1981 battle between Cold Crush and the Fantastic Romantic Five.
    - Cold Crush Brothers at Hoe Ave. Boys Club, 1981 (Box 9)
      Cold Crush strike a humorous pose on stage
    - DJ Charlie Chase Norman Thomas H.S., 1981 (Box 9)
      Charlie Chase with Tony Tone behind table with DJ equipment and record crates. In the background you see a rope separating the 'stage' from the crowd in the high school gym.
    - Cold Crush Brothers at Wild Style shoot, Dixie Club., 1981 (Box 9)
      Cold Crush Bros. performing at Dixie Club while being filmed for Charlie Ahearn's film Wild Style.
    - Cold Crush Bros. and Fantastic Romantic 5 Wild Style rehearsal, 1981 (Box 9)
      Cold Crush Bros. and Fantastic Romantic 5 rehearsing for the basketball court scene in Charlie Ahearn's film Wild Style. The basketball court was located at either Ryer Ave. and 182nd Street in the Bronx or at Intermediate School 115 (Morris Ave. and 184th).
    - Tony Tone, Afrika Bambaataa & Busy Bee at Bronx River, Zulu anniversary, 1981 (Box 9)
      Tony Tone in foreground with visible turn tables and microphone, and Afrika Bambaataa and Busy Bee in background.
    - Cold Crush Fever, 1981; Two copies (Box 9)
      Collage of Cold Crush photos with text: "Cold Crush Fever is here! Catch it now."
    - Charlie Chase and Tony Tone, 1982 (Box 9)
      The two Cold Crush DJs posing on street with crossed arms.
    - Almighty Kaygee & Disco King Mario (R.I.P) at Club Negril, N.Y.C., 1982 (Box 9)
      Kaygee stands in front of crowd, with Pioneering DJ Disco King Mario visible in crowd.
    - J.D.L at Club Negril, 1982 (Box 9)
      J.D.L performing on stage.
    - J.D.L., Harlem World, ca. 1982; Two copies (Box 9)
      J.D.L smoking a joint in front of the Harlem World mural. Taken at the Treacherous Three Anniversary, 1982 or 1983.
    - Grand Master Caz, J.D.L. and Kaygee at Harlem World, ca. 1982 (Box 9)
      Caz and Kaygee laughing as J.D.L goofs around at the Treacherous Three Anniversary, 1982 (or 1983?)
    - Grand Master Caz Norman Thomas H.S. Senior boat ride, 1982 (Box 9)
      From Cold Crush performance on the Norman Thomas High School senior trip to Bear Mountain on the Hudson River Day Line. (This line was later bought by the Circle Line).
    - Cold Crush Brothers and Treacherous Three, 1982 (Box 9)
      Members of Cold Crush Bros. and Treacherous Three posing in front of crowd on Day Line Boat. Norman Thomas H.S. Senior boat ride
    - Tony Tone and [Easy] A.D. at Norman Thomas H.S, 1982 (Box 9)
      Tony Tone and Easy A.D. posing on stage.
    - Almighty Kaygee, Harlem World, 1982; Framed Item 1
      Kay Gee throwing rolled up flyers/photos into the crowd. At the Harlem World Easter Show.
    - Grand Master Caz, J.D.L. and Kaygee at Harlem World, 1982; Framed Item 2
      Framed duplicate
    - Cold Crush Brothers, 1980; Framed Item 3
    - Grand Master Caz Norman Thomas H.S. Senior boat ride, 1982; Framed Item 4
    - Charlie Chase and Tony Tone, 1982; Framed Item 5
    - Easy A.D. & Tony Tone, 1981; Framed Item 6
    - Cold Crush Brothers and Treacherous Three, 1982; Framed Item 7
    - J.D.L at Club Negril, 1982; Framed Item 9
    - Tony Tone, Afrika Bambaataa & Busy Bee at Bronx River, Zulu anniversary, 1981; Framed Item 10
    - Almighty Kaygee & Disco King Mario (R.I.P) at Club Negril, N.Y.C., 1982; Framed Item 11
  - Large Format Prints - Bronx, N.Y. Scenes
    - Charlotte Street, Bronx, 1977 (Box 9)
      South Bronx devastation-- Rubble-filled vacant lot with buildings and large Puerto Rican flag in background
    - Boo Boo, South Bronx, 1978 (Box 9)
      Boy standing in large puddle with skateboard
    - South Bronx, 1977; Two copies (Box 9)
      Boy sitting on street with graffiti in background
    - South Bronx, 1979 (Box 9)
      Vacant lot behind abandoned buildings
    - South Bronx, 1979; Framed Item 13
    - Crotona Park, Bronx, 1980 (Box 9)
      Girl in crowd waving at camera
    - Treacherous Three, Norman Thomas H.S., 1981 (Box 9)
      Treacherous Three posing in front of high school bleachers
    - Busy Bee at Bronx River, Zulu Nation Anniversary, 1981 (Box 9)
      Busy Bee on stage
    - Loose Bruce with Crazy Legs in background, Club Negril, 1982 (Box 9)
      Three B-Boys (Shack Crew? Harlem World Crew?) dancing in front of crowd. Crazy Legs is visible in the background watching the performance.
    - Loose Bruce with Crazy Legs in background, Club Negril, 1982; Framed Item 8
  - 8 x 10 Prints - Modern, Reprints
    - Cold Crush Brothers, South Bronx High School, 1980; 8 prints (Box 10, Folder 1)
      Cold Crush performing at the 1980 South Bronx High School prom. This was Joe Conzo's prom.
    - Cold Crush Brothers, Harlem World, 1981-1982; 15 prints (Box 10, Folder 2)
      Cold Crush posing in suits in front of Harlem World mural
    - Cold Crush Brothers, Harlem World, 1981-1982; Inscribed "To Johan - Thanks for everything! Joe Conzo 2004" (Box 10, Folder 3)
      Cold Crush lined up posing in suits in front of Harlem World mural
    - J.D.L. and Grandmaster Caz, Harlem World, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      J.D.L. and Caz (in Rick James-style leather outfit) sharing a microphone onstage
    - Kool Moe Dee and Grandmaster Caz, Harlem World, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 5)
      Kool Moe Dee and Caz in the crowd at Harlem World
    - J.D.L., Harlem World, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Cold Crush Brothers, Harlem World, ca. 1981 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      Easy A.D., Kaygee, and [J.D.L.?] raising their arms in the air with their backs to the crowd
    - Printouts of photos from disc entitled "Tony Tone polaroids", ca. 1979 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      Color photos of Tony Tone and others, possibly taken by Angelo King
    - Cold Crush Brothers and South Bronx, ca. 1979-1981; 11x14 prints (Box 11)
      Various prints depicting Cold Crush Brothers performances and shots of the South Bronx
  - 8 x 10 Prints - Contemporary to original photo date
    - South Bronx, 1978; Mounted (Box 11)
      Broken fire hydrant and empty bottle of malt liquor
    - Joe Conzo - Self Portrait/Lighting Experiment, 1979; Mounted (Box 11)
      Posed shot of Joe holding flashbulbs with a hat covering his face
    - Paul Newman, March 24, 1980; Mounted (Box 11)
      Paul Newman chasing Joe and other protestors off of the set of the film Fort Apache, The Bronx. This was Joe's first published photograph; it appeared in the New York Post, March 25 1980. The film set was located at Eagle Ave. and Westchester Ave. in the Bronx. Community activists were protesting the film's negative depiction of minorities and of the Bronx in general. This print is accompanied by a mounted photocopy of the New York Post article with note from "Reyes II" of the UBP (United Bronx Parents) Photography Workshop congratulating Joe on its publication.
    - Vigil for John Lennon at Strawberry Fields, Central Park, ca. December 9, 1980; Mounted (Box 11)
      Mourners for John Lennon holding hands
    - Ben Gazzara at a protest of Fort Apache: The Bronx, Waldorf-Astoria Hotel, 1980; Mounted; Two copies (Box 11)
      The actor Ben Gazzara and an unidentified woman photographed outside the Waldorf-Astoria Hotel during a protest of the film Fort Apache, The Bronx.
    - Subway platform, Prospect Ave. and Westchester Ave., 1981; Mounted (Box 11)
      Man reading a newspaper while waiting for the train at the Prospect Ave. subway stop in the Bronx
    - Rachel, 1981; Mounted (Box 11)
      Portrait of Rachel; the back of her sister Abigail's head is also visible.
    - Sonia, 1981; Mounted (Box 11)
      Posed shot of Sonia
    - Empty matte board, 1981 (Box 11)
      Matte board from which a mounted photograph has been removed.
    - Evelina, 1984; Mounted (Box 11)
    - Three children, 1983; Mounted (Box 11)
      Portrait of three children
    - Jeanette "Chiquita" Otero, 1981; Mounted (Box 11)
    - Portrait, 1984; Mounted (Box 11)
      Portrait of unidentified woman
    - Tony Tone, LA Sunshine, and Grandmaster Caz, Harlem World, July 3, 1981; Signed on the front by Tony Tone, LA Sunshine, and Grandmaster Caz; dated on the back "July 3, 1981: Battle" (Box 10, Folder 9)
      Tony Tone and Grandmaster Caz of the Cold Crush Brothers pose with LA Sunshine of the Treacherous Three
    - Cold Crush Brothers, South Bronx High School, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      Cold Crush Brothers and the audience at the South Bronx High School gym
    - Inside the Botanica, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 11)
      Clerk behind the counter inside Botanica -- a store that sold religious supplies (rosaries, candles, etc.)
    - Cold Crush Brothers Studio Shot, 1982; Caption in red marker: These are the eighties and it [sic] all about C.C.: Cold Crush!! (Box 10, Folder 13)
      Posed picture of Cold Crush in suits
    - Grandmaster Flash and the Furious Five, ca. 1982 (Box 10, Folder 14)
      Posed studio shot of Grandmaster Flash and the Furious Five; photographer unknown. Sugarhill Records publicity photo.
    - Kurtis Blow and Melle Mel, ca. 1983; Note in red marker on back reads "Marie Moore, Amsterdam New, 2340 8th Ave., 5th Flr - By [Hard?]". Blue pen note reads "Grandmaster Flash"; possibly Flash's signature. (Box 10, Folder 12)
      Kurtis Blow and Melle Mel looking at a magazine article on Grandmaster Flash and the Furious Five, possibly at the Amsterdam New, 2340 8th Ave, 4th floor. Photograph by Gary Gershoff.
    - 5 Additions, ca. 1983 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - 8 x 10" photographs, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - 8 x 10" photographs, Undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Mounted and assorted sizes, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - 4 x 6 Prints - Cold Crush Brothers
    - Cold Crush Brothers and fans at T-Connection, 1979; 17 prints (Box 12, Folder 1)
      Early Joe Conzo photos of Cold Crush-- possibly the first. Also several shots of people from the audience (friends of Joe Conzo); one shot of Tony Tone with his mother; one shot of Cold Crush's DJ equipment.
    - Roseland Ballroom, 1980; 6 prints (Box 12, Folder 2)
      The Fearless Four onstage; Money Ray, Joe Conzo, Easy A.D. and friends in the audience.
    - Cold crush Brothers, South Bronx H.S., ca. 1980; 15 prints (Box 12, Folder 3)
      Cold Crush performance at South Bronx High School in 1980 with additional pictures of the Treacherous 3, Kool Moe Dee, Cracker Jack of the Casanova Crew, and King. A photograph from this show was used (without permission) in the film CB4.
    - Cold Crush Brothers, South Bronx H.S. Prom, 1980; 17 prints (Box 12, Folder 4)
      Cold Crush performing at the 1980 South Bronx High School prom. Joe Conzo, Easy A.D., and Tony Tone attended South Bronx HS; this was Joe's prom.
    - Cold Crush van ride (Tony Tone's van) upstate NY, 1980; 9 prints (Box 12, Folder 5)
      Joe Conzo, Cold Crush Brothers, Nana (Tony Tone's cousin), King (Tony Tone's brother), Money Ray, and [Kool Moe Dee], driving upstate in Tony Tone's van. Joe claims that Kool Moe Dee was not present in the van, so we are waiting for identification on the last individual.
    - Cold Crush, Skate Palace (onstage), 1981; 17 prints (Box 12, Folder 6)
      Cold Crush performance at the Skatin' Palace in 1981.
    - Cold Crush, Skate Palace (backstage), 1981; 5 prints (Box 12, Folder 7)
      Cold Crush backstage at the Skatin' Palace, 1981.
    - Cold Crush and Loose Bruce, Club Negril's, 1981; 23 prints (Box 12, Folder 8)
      Shots of Cold Crush performing and some shots of b-boy Loose Bruce dancing. Before Cold Crush J.D.L. and Grand Master Caz performed together as the Notorious Two. There are several silhouette shots of Caz and J.D.L. together in this group, and though this is a Cold Crush performance, Joe Conzo refers to these photos in this group as shots of the Notorious Two.
    - Charlie Chase, Afrika Bambaataa, Grand Mixer DST, Kips Bay Boys Club, 1981; 1 prints (Box 12, Folder 9)
      Charlie Chase, Afrika Bambaataa, and Grand Mixer DST at the Kips Bay Boys Club, 1981.
    - Cold Crush, Electricians' Hall (Amityville, Long Island), 1981; 1 prints (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Cold Crush at the Fever (167th and Jerome), 1981; 12 prints (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Cold Crush Harlem World Easter Show, 1981; 50 prints (Box 12, Folder 12)
      This group of photos is a very detailed recording of the 1981 performance of Cold Crush at Harlem World. Shots from this show are identifiable because of the use of a smoke machine onstage.
    - Cold Crush and the Treacherous Three, Norman Thomas H.S, 1981; 9 prints (Box 12, Folder 13)
      Cold Crush and the Treacherous Three perform at Norman Thomas High School in 1981. Also several posed shots of both groups in front of the gym bleachers.
    - Cold Crush upstairs at Harlem World, 1981; 12 prints (Box 12, Folder 14)
      Cold Crush rehearsing upstairs at Harlem World before a show in 1981.
    - Cold Crush, Hoe Ave. Boys Club, 1981; 6 prints (Box 12, Folder 15)
      Cold Crush performance at Roosevelt H.S. with pictures of crowd and members.
    - Cold Crush Brothers and Fantastic Romantic Five 'Wild Style' Rehearsals, 1981; 13 prints (Box 12, Folder 16)
      The Cold Crush Brothers and Fantastic Romantic 5 rehearsing for Charlie Ahearn's film 'Wild Style' basketball court scene. The basketball court was located at either Ryer Ave. and 182nd Street in the Bronx OR at Intermediate School 115 (Morris Ave. and 184th). Some shots focus on Kevie Kev and Whipper Whip (of the Fantastic Five); Charlie Ahearn and Fab Five Freddy are also visible.
    - Cold Crush Brothers and Charlie Ahearn signing the 'Wild Style' contract, Dixie Club, 1981; 8 prints (Box 12, Folder 17)
      Cold Crush and Charlie Ahearn sign the contract for Ahearn's film Wild Style.
    - Cold Crush Brothers Hoe Ave Boys Club, 1981; 22 prints (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Cold Crush Brothers and Fantastic Romantic Five battle, Harlem World, 1981; 13 prints (Box 12, Folder 19)
      Pictures of the Cold Crush Brothers performance in the famous battle with the Fantastic Romantic Five.
    - Cold Crush Brothers, South Bronx High School, 1981; 2 prints (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Zulu Nation Anniversary, Bronx River, 1981; 4 prints (Box 12, Folder 21)
      Tony Tone, DJ Red Alert, J.D.L., Grand Master Caz, Mr. Biggs (of the Soul Sonic Force) and Busy Bee at the 1981 Zulu Nation Anniversary.
    - Cold Crush Portraits, 1981; 3 prints (Box 12, Folder 22)
      Three portrait photos taken on Prospect Ave. and 156th street in the Bronx.
    - Cold Crush Brothers studio portraits, 1981; 101 prints (Box 12, Folder 23)
      A large number of posed group, solo, and duo shots of the Cold Crush Brothers. These portraits were taken in a makeshift studio in the back room of United Bronx Parents in the Bronx.
    - Cold Crush Brothers, Harlem World, 1981-1982; 35 prints (Box 12, Folder 24)
      Posed and performance shots of Cold Crush Brothers (in suits)
    - Cold Crush Brothers, Harlem World, 1982; 24 prints (Box 12, Folder 25)
      Wide shots of the stage during a Cold Crush performance at Harlem World
    - Norman Thomas High School Senior Boat Ride, 1982; 6 prints (Box 12, Folder 26)
      From Cold Crush performance on the Norman Thomas High School senior trip to Bear Mountain on the Hudson River Day Line. (This line was later bought by the Circle Line). Also included: one shot of LA Sunshine (of the Treacherous Three) with members of Cold Crush; several shots of students/audience on boat
    - Treacherous Three Anniversary - Cold Crush Brothers, Jazzy Ace and D-Ski, Wayne and Charlie; Harlem World, 1982-1983; 39 prints (Box 12, Folder 27)
      Shots of performances by Cold Crush, Jazzy Ace and D-Ski, and hip hop ventriloquist act Wayne and Charlie at the Treacherous Three anniversary in either 1982 or 1983. Also: two pictures of Tony Tone's brother King in the crowd.
    - Cold Crush - Wild Style Filming, Dixie Club, 1981; 3 prints (Box 12, Folder 28)
      These pictures show the filming of a scene for Wild Style. The film crew is visible in the crowd.
  - 4 x 6 Prints - Bronx, N.Y. Scenes
    - United Bronx Parents Picnic, 1978-1979; 17 prints (Box 13, Folder 1)
      Photos of unidentified individuals from a UBP picnic in 1978. Also one picture of Joe's girlfriend Teresa.
    - Fort Apache: The Bronx' Protest, March 24th, 1980; 5 prints (Box 13, Folder 2)
      Paul Newman chasing Joe and other protestors off of the set of the film Fort Apache, The Bronx. This was Joe's first published photograph; it appeared in the New York Post, March 25 1980. The film set was located at Eagle Ave. and Westchester Ave. in the Bronx. Community activists were protesting the film's negative depiction of minorities and of the Bronx in general.
    - Tito Puente and Machito outdoor performance, ca.1980; 15 prints (Box 13, Folder 3)
      Photos of Tito Puente and Machito on stage outdoors in the Bronx. Several photos of Tito and Machito performing, some shots of the crowd, and two photos of filmmaker Carlos Ortiz and his film crew. Ortiz was one of Joe Conzo's mentors, and directed a documentary about Machito.
    - Vigil for John Lennon at Strawberry Fields, Central Park, ca. December 9, 1980; 1 prints (Box 13, Folder 4)
      Two young girls mourning John Lennon in Central Park
    - Mean Machine' outdoor event, 3rd Ave Hub, 1981; 32 prints (Box 13, Folder 5)
      Photos of Mean Machine during an outdoor event sponsored by the radio station 92 KTV at the 3rd Ave Hub in the Bronx. The photos include a few pictures of the group onstage, but most are of individuals in the audience.
    - Government Cheese handout, United Bronx Parents, 1982; 12 prints (Box 13, Folder 6)
      Residents of the Bronx waiting in line to pick up free government cheese at United Bronx Parents.
    - South Bronx Photography, 1978-1979; 52 prints (Box 13, Folder 7)
      Photos of various locations in the Bronx in various locations, particularly along Prospect Avenue above 149th St. Some of the photos depict early graffiti and street art. Many street portraits of unidentified individuals. One print depicts a 1978 protest of funding cuts for sports programs in South Bronx high schools. One shot of a vacant lot at Westchester Ave. and Brook Ave. was used as the cover image for the book Next Stop: Growing Up Wild Style by Ivan Sanchez (Touchstone, 2008).
    - South Bronx Street Scenes, 1979; 49 prints (Box 13, Folder 8)
      Photos of everyday street scenes scattered all over the Bronx. Photos depicting stores, street vendors, people walking, and children playing. There are also several shots of a film crew working on an unidentified documentary.
    - South Bronx Street Scenes, 1981-1983; 13 prints (Box 13, Folder 9)
      These photos depict demolished buildings and vacant lots-- the devastation of the South Bronx. Also included are photos from the Cloisters in Manhattan, Lincoln Hospital, and the 1981 or 1982 Puerto Rican Day parade.
    - Joe Conzo Portraits, 1976-1983; 74 prints (Box 13, Folder 10)
      This roll includes Joe's earliest black and white shots-- pictures of his classmates at Junior H.S 149 from 1976. Also included are pictures of Joe's girlfriend Teresa and her nieces, Joe's girlfriend Maria, Abigail and Rachel (two sisters from the Bronx), Sonya, Tiny and Herman (Tiny is the daughter of Carmen Arroyo, the first Hispanic woman in NY assembly), Sandy Santiago and Dr. Sporano from Lincoln Hospital, Carlos, Cappy, Roseann Pascale (a college friend of Joe's who now produces the television show Miami Ink), David, and several unidentified children from the South Bronx. The last photo in this group is two unidentified individuals who may have been radio DJs; they seem to be in a radio station or record store.
    - United Bronx Parents Portraits, ca. 1979-1981; 11 prints (Box 13, Folder 11)
      These portraits are of various people in or outside the office of United Bronx Parents including. Named individuals include Reuben and Yvette, Evelina Antonetty (Founder of U.B.P. and Joe Conzo's grandmother), and Donald Antonetty. There are also several color shots from a UBP party in 1976, including a shot of two vendors who provided food for a summer lunch program.
    - Joe Conzo personal photos, 1978-1982; 67 prints (Box 13, Folder 12)